Guide to the Dan Miller Photographs Collection PHOTOS.120
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Unions.
  - Subseries I:C: Amalgamated Meatcutters and Butcher Workmen.
    - Local 342, Faulty Steps [Total negs: 5], Dec 8, 1966 (Box 5, Item 8981)
    - Local 342, Shop Stewards Meeting, International Hotel, Huntington [Total negs: 25], Jan 8, 1967 (Box 5, Item 8985)
    - Local 342, Progress Photo Building [Total negs: 14], Jan 19, 1967 (Box 5, Item 8987)
    - Local 342, Negotiation, International Hotel [Total negs: 13], Jan 20, 1967 (Box 5, Item 8988)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School, State Education, Lew [?] Denenatic [?] [Total negs: 18], Feb 2, 1967 (Box 5, Item 8990)
    - Local 342, New Members Class, Huntington [Total negs: 21], Mar 8, 1967 (Box 5, Item 8991)
    - Local 342, Pensioners, Brooklyn [Total negs: 15], Mar 14, 1967 (Box 5, Item 8992)
    - Local 342, Progress Photo,New Building [Total negs: 7], Mar 28, 1967 (Box 5, Item 8993)
    - Local 342, Membership Meeting, International Hotel, Huntington [Total negs: 35], Apr 10, 1967 (Box 5, Item 8995)
    - Local 342, Community Service, Commodore Hotel [Total negs: 17], Apr 15, 1967 (Box 5, Item 8996)
    - Local 342, Safety Meeting, International Hotel [Total negs: 8], Apr 18, 1967 (Box 5, Item 8997)
    - Local 342, Blood Bank, Jamaica, Shop Stewards, Brooklyn [Total negs: 22], Apr 24, 1967 (Box 5, Item 8998)
    - Local 342, Blood Bank, Brooklyn [These negatives are originally dated 4/31/1967. As April only has 30 days, the date has been rendered 4/30/1967.] [Total negs: 17], Apr 30, 1967 (Box 5, Item 8994)
    - Local 342, Shop Stewards Meeting, Huntington [Total negs: 24], May 1, 1967 (Box 5, Item 8999)
    - Local 342, Sobena Arb's [?] Trip to Europe, Hotel Geneda [?], Membership Meeting, Contracts [Total negs: 46], May 8, 1967 (Box 5, Item 9000)
    - Local 342, Maimonides Hospital, Platelet Center, Progress Photo, New Building [Total negs: 22], May 16, 1967 (Box 5, Item 9001)
    - Local 342, Petition Signing, Brooklyn [Total negs: 11], May 23, 1967 (Box 5, Item 9002)
    - Local 342, Labor Management Exhibit, Roosevelt Field [Total negs: 85], May 26, 1967 (Box 5, Item 9003)
    - Local 342, Congress Women, Brooklyn Office [Total negs: 24], Jun 5, 1967 (Box 5, Item 9004)
    - Local 342, Brooklyn Pension Checks [Total negs: 18], Jun 13, 1967 (Box 5, Item 9005)
    - Local 342, Safety Committee, Jamaica Office [Total negs: 9], Jun 26, 1967 (Box 5, Item 9006)
    - Local 342, Trimaches Restaurant, Staten Island, Political Action Conference [Total negs: 22], Jun 26, 1967 (Box 5, Item 9007)
    - Local 342, Photo of New Building for Key Chain [Total negs: 14], Jul 25, 1967 (Box 5, Item 9009)
    - Local 342, Moving to New Building [Total negs: 17], Jul 26, 1967 (Box 5, Item 9010)
    - Local 342, Blood Bank, Jamaica [?], Apprentices [Total negs: 14], Jul 27, 1967 (Box 5, Item 9008)
    - Local 342, Executive Groups, Jamaica [Total negs: 74], Aug 22, 1967 (Box 5, Item 9011)
    - Local 342, Business Agents in Action, Pre-Retirement Course [Total negs: 285], Aug 23, 1967 (Box 5, Item 9012)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School, Credit [?] Union [?], Office Photos [Total negs: 48], Sep 1967 (Box 6, Item 9018)
    - Local 342, Unity Hospital New Building, Dental Photos, Melchiorre Family [Total negs: 21], Sep 1967 (Box 6, Item 9019)
    - Local 342, Reunion Photo, Phil Dr. [?] Photo, East Meadow [Total negs: 13], Sep 11, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9013)
    - Local 342, Official Oppening, New Building, A & P Bookkeeper [Total negs: 120], Sep 13, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9014)
    - Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Josepl Belsky [Total negs: 3], Sep 14, 1967 (Box 2, Item 8885)
    - Local 342, Community Services, Jamaica [Total negs: 12], Sep 19, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9015)
    - Local 342, Staten Island Office, Veronica Food Farm, Dolly Obrensky [?] [Total negs: 13], Sep 20, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9016)
    - Local 342, Shop Steward Dinner [?], Sheraton - Hilton [Total negs: 59], Sep 30, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9017)
    - Local 342, COPE [?] Committee, Huntington [Total negs: 23], Oct 3, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9020)
    - Local 342, A & P Bookkeepers, Jamaica [Total negs: 26], Oct 10, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9021)
    - Local 342, Blood Bank, Jamaica [Total negs: 29], Oct 16, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9022)
    - Local 342, Pre-Retirement, Jamaica [Total negs: 18], Oct 17, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9023)
    - Local 342, COPE Prizes Jamaica [Total negs: 6], Oct 30, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9024)
    - Local 342, 20 Year P[?], Jamaica [Total negs: 55], Nov 1, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9025)
    - Local 342, Elections, International Hotel and Huntington [Total negs: 96], Nov 5, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9026)
    - Local 342, 20 year. [?], Suffolk County, Jamaica [?] [Total negs: 21], Nov 29, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9028)
    - Local 342, First Retirement Senior, Huntington [Total negs: 34], Dec 6, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9029)
    - Local 342, Safety Meeting [Total negs: 35], Dec 12, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9030)
    - Local 342, Installation [Total negs: 33], Dec 13, 1967 (Box 6, Item 9031)
    - Local 342, A & P Membership Contract Meetings, Republic Lodge and International Hotel [Total negs: 31], May 21, 1905 (Box 1, Item 8844)
    - Local 342, A & P Membership Contract Meetings, Republic Lodge and International Hotel [Total negs: 5], May 21, 1905 (Box 1, Item 8845)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School, Committee of Markets Gerard Weisberg [Total negs: 23], Jan 3, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9032)
    - Local 342, Blood Bank Apprentice School New Members Class [Total negs: 28], Jan 8, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9033)
    - Local 342, Shop Stewards Meeting, Republic Lodge & Jamaica [Total negs: 82], Jan 9, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9034)
    - Local 342, Furriers Consumers Meeting [?], Hilton [Total negs: 20], Jan 13, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9035)
    - Local 342, COPE [?] Meeting Jamaica & Huntington [Total negs: 20], Jan 15, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9036)
    - Local 342, B to A Membership Cards [?], Vinnie [?] [Total negs: 18], Jan 29, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9037)
    - Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Bill Gefner Portrait, Abe Feingloss, Executive Blood Group, Contract Meeting Brooklyn, NY [Total negs: 57], Feb 6, 1968 (Box 2, Item 8886)
    - Local 342, [?] School Safety. [Total negs: 11], Feb 6, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9038)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School [Total negs: 21], Feb 7, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9039)
    - Local 342, Pre-Retirement, Huntington [Total negs: 26], Feb 14, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9040)
    - Local 342, Bert [?] Podell, Brooklyn [Total negs: 7], Feb 20, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9041)
    - Local 342, Credit Union Apprentice [?] Renewal [Total negs: 28], Feb 26, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9042)
    - Local 342, Pre-Retirement Builder Photo, Brooklyn [?] [Total negs: 35], Mar 5, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9043)
    - Local 342, Blood Bank, Brooklyn [Total negs: 18], Mar 11, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9044)
    - Local 342, Senior Citizens Pension Checks [Total negs: 30], Mar 12, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9045)
    - Local 342, Old Building, Menid [?] Blvd., Sutfin [?] Building, Queens, Before & After Photos [#] 842 [Total negs: 37], Mar 14, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9046)
    - Local 342, Women Committee, First Meeting, Safety Meeting, COPE[?] Meeting [Total negs: 22], Mar 18, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9047)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School, Senior Citizens [Total negs: 24], Mar 20, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9048)
    - Local 342, [#] 846 Blood Bank, Staten Island [Total negs: 18], Mar 20, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9049)
    - Local 342, International Hotel, Membership Meeting,Republic Lodge [?] [Total negs: 69], Mar 26, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9050)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School Manpower C[?] & [?] Agency [Total negs: 20], Mar 26, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9051)
    - Local 342, Pre-Retirement, First Graduation, Huntington [Total negs: 26], Mar 27, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9052)
    - Local 342, A & P Shop Stewards Contract Meetings, Jamaica & Huntington [Total negs: 42], Apr 1, 1968 (Box 1, Item 8841)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School Graduation, Jamaica [Total negs: 32], Apr 5, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9053)
    - Local 342, Community Services, Commidore Hotel [Total negs: 10], Apr 6, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9054)
    - Local 342, Executive Board New York [?], School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell University [Total negs: 19], Apr 10, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9055)
    - Local 342, Trophy Winner Barbara Joynes A & P [Total negs: 9], Apr 15, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9056)
    - Local 342, "Meet Your Supervisor Nite" Jerome Ambro Hunt [?] [Total negs: 13], Apr 15, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9057)
    - Local 342, Blood Bank Jamaica [Total negs: 11], Apr 15, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9059)
    - Local 342, New Member Class Jamaica [Total negs: 15], Apr 22, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9060)
    - Local 342, Final Instruction Cornell University Jamaica [Total negs: 13], May 1, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9058)
    - Local 342, Women [?], Jamaica [Total negs: 36], May 15, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9061)
    - Local 342, Women's Activities, Staten Island [Total negs: 16], May 19, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9062)
    - Local 342, Blood Bank, Huntington, [?] Oaks [Total negs: 13], May 27, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9063)
    - Local 342, Farm Workers Meeting, Jamaica, Safety Meeting & First Aid (Newspaper Award Plaque) [Total negs: 47], Jun 3, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9064)
    - Local 342, Senior Citizen Bus Ride to Sterling Garden [Total negs: 6], Jun 16, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9066)
    - Local 342, Boat Ride & Picnic, Bear Mountain [Total negs: 62], Jun 23, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9065)
    - Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Convention, San Diego, CA [Total negs: 774], Jul 7, 1968 (Box 2, Item 8888)
    - Local 342, A & P Shop Stewards Meeting, Jamaica [Total negs: 20], Jul 23, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9067)
    - Local 342, A & P Contract Meetings, Republic Lodge [Total negs: 49], Jul 28, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9068)
    - Local 342, A & P Contract Meetings, International Hotel Stuart Kay, Al Pisano, 30and31 - Emil Pisani [Total negs: 50], Jul 29, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9069)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School Graduation, Jamaica [Total negs: 34], Aug 16, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9070)
    - Local 342, Senior Citizens Bus to Atlantic City [Total negs: 24], Aug 22, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9071)
    - Local 342, General Membership Meeting, Dues Increase [?] [Total negs: 93], Aug 25, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9072)
    - Local 342, Women Committee's, Staten Island [Total negs: 11], Sep 4, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9073)
    - Local 342, Safety Meeting Jamaica [Total negs: 20], Sep 9, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9074)
    - Local 342, Pre-Retirement Jamaica [Total negs: 16], Sep 10, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9075)
    - Local 342, Safety and COPE [?] Jamaica [Total negs: 26], Sep 16, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9076)
    - Local 342, [?] [?] to Vietnam Staten Island [Total negs: 19], Sep 18, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9077)
    - Local 342, Apprentice Manager Floyd P [?] Parkers [Total negs: 14], Oct 7, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9078)
    - Local 342, Women's Committee, Huntington [Total negs: 17], Oct 7, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9079)
    - Local 342, Check to Cong. Woolf. [Total negs: 34], Oct 10, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9080)
    - Local 342, Senator Javitz, 110 E 45th St. [Total negs: 16], Oct 15, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9081)
    - Local 342, Safety Meeting, Huntington [Total negs: 11], Oct 21, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9083)
    - Local 342, Drugs, Staten Island [Total negs: 13], Oct 23, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9084)
    - Local 342, Area Meeting, Womens, Jamaica [Total negs: 18], Oct 28, 1968 (Box 1, Item 8832)
    - Local 342, [?] Drawing [Total negs: 22], Oct 30, 1968 (Box 1, Item 8833)
    - Local 342, Long Island, Federal of Labor "Humphrey" [?] Levittown [?] [Total negs: 65], Nov 2, 1968 (Box 1, Item 8834)
    - Local 342, Otto [?], Senior Citizens Dinner, Dance, Jamaica [Total negs: 54], Nov 2, 1968 (Box 1, Item 8835)
    - Local 342, Drugs, Jamaica Office [Total negs: 23], Nov 18, 1968 (Box 7, Item 9082)
    - Local 342, Building, Games for Orphan Christmas Party [Total negs: 13], Nov 19, 1968 (Box 1, Item 8836)
    - Local 342, New Members, Staten Island [Total negs: 14], Nov 24, 1968 (Box 1, Item 8837)
    - Local 342, Arts & Crafts, Senior Citizens [Total negs: 22], Nov 25, 1968 (Box 1, Item 8838)
    - Local 342, Orphan Christmas Party, Jamaica [Total negs: 105], Dec 8, 1968 (Box 1, Item 8840)
    - Local 342, Graduation Pre-Retirement, Huntington [Total negs: 19], Dec 11, 1968 (Box 1, Item 8842)
    - Local 342, "Food Council" [?], Champs [Total negs: 18], Dec 18, 1968 (Box 1, Item 8843)
    - Local 342, Gift Wrapping for Orphan Party, Jamaica, Huntington, Brooklyn, Staten Island [Total negs: 49], Dec 23, 1968 (Box 1, Item 8839)
    - Local 342, Portraits: Irving Stern [?], Moe Fliss [?] [Total negs: 24], May 22, 1905 (Box 19, Item 11715)
    - Local 342, Safety & Women's Committee, Jamaica [Total negs: 22], Jan 6, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8846)
    - Local 342, First Review, Class 8 Apprentices [Total negs: 8], Jan 9, 1969 (Box 5, Item 8986)
    - Local 342, A & P Shop Stewards (Contracts), Jamaica [Total negs: 14], Jan 13, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8847)
    - Local 342, Safety Management, Jamaica [Total negs: 38], Jan 16, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8848)
    - Local 342, Safety, Members Credit Union [Total negs: 10], Jan 22, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8849)
    - Local 342, Apprentice Blood Bank [Total negs: 12], Jan 27, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8850)
    - Local 342, A & P Shop Stewards, Huntington [Total negs: 15], Jan 28, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8851)
    - Local 342, A & P Shop Stewards, Staten Island [Total negs: 19], Feb 3, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8852)
    - Local 342, General Membership Meetings, International Hotel, Patchogue [?] [Total negs: 36], Feb 5, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8853)
    - Local 342, Safety Apprentice School [Total negs: 53], Feb 14, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8854)
    - Local 342, COPE [?], Brooklyn Office [?] [?] [Total negs: 12], Feb 17, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8855)
    - Local 342, Jamaica Recall, A & B Meeting, COPE [?] [Total negs: 19], Feb 24, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8856)
    - Local 342, First Annual Mass & Communion Breakfast, Jamaica [Total negs: 32], Mar 9, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8857)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School, Class Orientation [Total negs: 17], Mar 14, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8858)
    - Local 342, Credit Union, Jamaica [Total negs: 5], Mar 17, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8859)
    - Local 342, Drugs, Dolessio [?], Post Staten Island [Total negs: 16], Mar 19, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8860)
    - Local 342, Blood Bank, Jamaica [Total negs: 20], Mar 25, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8861)
    - Local 342, Women's Committee, Jamaica [Total negs: 17], Mar 26, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8862)
    - Local 342, First Sports Meeting, Jamaica [Total negs: 12], Apr 7, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8863)
    - Local 342, Joint Union & Safety Committee, Jamaica [Total negs: 81], Apr 9, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8864)
    - Local 342, Senior Citizens Pension Clerks, Huntington [Total negs: 11], Apr 10, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8865)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School Graduation, Jamaica [Total negs: 29], Apr 11, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8866)
    - Local 342, New York City Central Labor Council, Commodore Hotel [Total negs: 24], Apr 12, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8867)
    - Local 342, Huntington COPE [Total negs: 20], Apr 21, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8868)
    - Local 342, Drugs, Staten Island [Total negs: 11], Apr 22, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8869)
    - Local 342, A & P Book Keepers, Jamaica [Total negs: 14], Apr 22, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8870)
    - Local 342, A & P Book Keepers Luncheon, Huntington [Total negs: 23], Apr 23, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8871)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School Visitors [Total negs: 12], Apr 29, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8872)
    - Local 342, Blood Bank, Huntington [Total negs: 14], May 5, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8873)
    - Local 342, Softball, Long Island [Total negs: 33], May 11, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8874)
    - Local 342, Women Committee, Breast Cancer, Dr. Gold, Dr. [?] [Total negs: 15], May 12, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8875)
    - Local 342, Apprentice Blood Bank, Red Cross Building [Total negs: 37], May 12, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8876)
    - Local 342, Bowling Awards Womens Committee, Staten Island [Total negs: 23], May 19, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8877)
    - Local 342, Cornell University [?] School Problems [Total negs: 10], May 27, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8879)
    - Local 342, Safety, Management [Total negs: 11], May 27, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8880)
    - Local 342, Narcotics, Huntington [Total negs: 11], Jun 2, 1969 (Box 1, Item 8881)
    - Local 342, Apprentice Graduation, Jamaica [Total negs: 49], Nov 10, 1969 (Box 6, Item 9027)
    - Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Iowa Beef, A & P Stores [Total negs: 48], Mar 28, 1970 (Box 2, Item 8889)
    - Local 888, Scholarship Award [Total negs: 8], Aug 4, 1971 (Box 11, Item 11686)
    - Amalgamated Industrial Union Group and Portraits [Total negs: 65], Nov 1, 1989 (Box 2, Item 8887)
  - Subseries I:D: American Federation of Musicians.
    - Local 132, 40th Anniversary Color [Total negs: 92], Nov 12, 1977 (Box 11, Item 11690)
    - Local 802, Max Aaron's Office [Total negs: 23], Oct 20, 1980 (Box 11, Item 11691)
    - Kamber Group [Total negs: 24], Mar 15, 1989 (Box 11, Item 11687)
    - Kamber Group Portrait, Caslberry Musician's Union [Total negs: 27], May 16, 1989 (Box 11, Item 11688)
    - Kamber Group, American Federation of Musicians Pension Fund [Total negs: 35], Jul 13, 1989 (Box 11, Item 11689)
  - Subseries I:E: American Federation of Teachers.
    - Jerry Cammorta on Maternity Leave, (Print #20A) Male "Maternity" Leave [Total negs: 3], Feb 1974 (Box 8, Item 11424)
    - Mondale Rally CO-OP City [Total negs: 41], Mar 31, 1984 (Box 12, Item 11702)
    - Central Harlem Intermediate School Elaine Smith Dance [Total negs: 47], Jun 5, 1984 (Box 12, Item 11703)
    - Harry Truman High School Museum for Migrating People [Total negs: 96], Jun 6, 1984 (Box 12, Item 11704)
  - Subseries I:F: American Postal Union.
    - Moe Biller Dinner [Total negs: 80], Jun 2, 1989 (Box 12, Item 11705)
  - Subseries I:G: Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers International Union, Local 50.
    - Presentations [Total negs: 19], Aug 25, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11707)
    - Executive Board Dinner Chos [?] French Restaurant [Total negs: 37], Dec 15, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11708)
    - Staff Meeting [Total negs: 7], Jan 8, 1971 (Box 12, Item 11710)
    - Presentation, Manhattan Hotel [Total negs: 10], Mar 30, 1971 (Box 12, Item 11709)
    - Christmas, Hotel Commodore [?] [Total negs: 47], Dec 14, 1971 (Box 8, Item 11552)
    - Executive Board Dinner, Hotel Commodore [Total negs: 70], Dec 19, 1972 (Box 8, Item 11553)
    - Installation Dinner, Commodore Hotel [Total negs: 99], Dec 17, 1974 (Box 8, Item 11554)
    - Christmas-Retirement [Total negs: 86], Dec 16, 1975 (Box 8, Item 11555)
  - Subseries I:H: Building Service Employees International Union, Local 307.
    - Installation of Officers Plummer Hall [Total negs: 6], Dec 7, 1970 (Box 8, Item 11581)
    - Portrait: Paul Gamaldi [Total negs: 37], Jun 26, 1972 (Box 8, Item 11582)
  - Subseries I:I: Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 45.
    - Manhattan Center, General Membership Meeting [Total negs: 39], May 27, 1905 (Box 8, Item 11596)
    - Cornell University, First Class [Total negs: 18], Apr 30, 1974 (Box 8, Item 11593)
    - Luchow's [?] [Total negs: 9], Aug 29, 1974 (Box 8, Item 11592)
    - General Membership Meeting Diplomat Hotel [Total negs: 33], Nov 19, 1974 (Box 8, Item 11594)
    - Christmas-Senior Citizens [Total negs: 39], Dec 19, 1974 (Box 8, Item 11595)
  - Subseries I:J: Civil Service Employees Association.
    - Hilton, Breakfast Delegate Meeting, Representative Gebhardt and Union Meeting [separated from b/w] [Total negs: 121], undated (Box 12, Item 11701)
    - [CSEA] New York State Department of Transportation Demonstration, Politicians with laid off Members Assemblywoman Nolan [Total negs: 36], Sep 27, 1996 (Box 12, Item 11699)
    - Hilton, Breakfast Delegate Meeting Rep. Gebhardt and Union Leadership [separated from color] [Total negs: 53], Oct 3, 1996 (Box 12, Item 11700)
  - Subsiers I:K: Federation of Catholic Teachers.
    - Catholic Teachers Demonstration [Total negs: 17], Sep 3, 1980 (Box 12, Item 11747)
    - Federation of Catholic Teachers Scholarships [Total negs: 9], Jul 30, 1983 (Box 12, Item 11748)
  - Subseries I:L: Fur, Leather, and Machine Workers Union.
    - Furriers Joint Council Greek Local 70 Manhattan Center Dance [Total negs: 54], Jan 25, 1964 (Box 13, Item 11795)
    - Furriers Joint Board: Negro History Week Fashion Institute of Technology [Total negs: 50], Feb 15, 1964 (Box 13, Item 11796)
    - Furriers Joint Board Belleview Hospital -- Easter Party [Total negs: 14], Mar 24, 1964 (Box 13, Item 11797)
    - Furriers Joint Council Greek Rally [Total negs: 33], Apr 16, 1964 (Box 13, Item 11798)
    - Furriers Joint Council Rosoffs [?] -- Josfer [?] Stafsly [?] dinner [Total negs: 52], May 7, 1964 (Box 13, Item 11799)
    - Furriers Joint Council Elections [Total negs: 23], Jun 17, 1964 (Box 13, Item 11800)
    - Furriers Joint Board Strike Photos [Total negs: 10], Jul 1, 1964 (Box 14, Item 11801)
    - Furriers Joint Board Democratic Convention Atlantic City [Total negs: 41], Aug 26, 1964 (Box 14, Item 11802)
    - Furriers Joint Board Christmas Party [Total negs: 25], Dec 12, 1964 (Box 14, Item 11803)
    - Furriers Joint Council New Contract Meeting [Total negs: 37], Dec 14, 1964 (Box 14, Item 11805)
    - Furriers Joint Council Christmas Party [Total negs: 36], Dec 19, 1964 (Box 14, Item 11806)
    - Furriers Joint Board the 1965 Elections-Issues and Candidates [Total negs: 31], May 18, 1905 (Box 14, Item 11815)
    - Furriers Joint Council Local 70 Award Dance [Total negs: 39], Jan 23, 1965 (Box 14, Item 11807)
    - Furriers Joint Board 50th Anniversary Ben Pinsley [Total negs: 85], Feb 13, 1965 (Box 14, Item 11808)
    - Furriers Joint Council Mass Meeting (contract) Manhattan Center [Total negs: 56], Feb 19, 1965 (Box 14, Item 11809)
    - Furriers Joint Board Petition Signing [Total negs: 20], Mar 25, 1965 (Box 14, Item 11810)
    - Furriers Joint Council Dinner for Obe Finegloss [?] [Total negs: 54], May 1, 1965 (Box 14, Item 11811)
    - Furriers Joint Board Statler Hilton Group Photos [Total negs: 9], May 11, 1965 (Box 14, Item 11812)
    - Furriers Joint Board Membership Meeting Statler Hilton [Total negs: 52], Oct 14, 1965 (Box 14, Item 11813)
    - Furriers Joint Board Christmas Party [Total negs: 29], Dec 11, 1965 (Box 14, Item 11804)
    - Joint Board pensioners Christmas Party [Total negs: 11], Dec 23, 1965 (Box 14, Item 11814)
    - Full Day Plan. [?] [Total negs: 144], Apr 23, 1969 (Box 12, Item 11750)
    - Elections [Total negs: 15], May 22, 1969 (Box 12, Item 11749)
    - Blood Bank and Group Photo [Total negs: 35], May 26, 1969 (Box 12, Item 11752)
    - Joint Board Peace Rally 7th Ave. & 28th St. [Total negs: 61], Oct 15, 1969 (Box 12, Item 11751)
    - Joint Board Iowa Beef Button [?] Hudson Bay Auditorium [?] New York Ratification Meeting [Total negs: 47], Jan 5, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11754)
    - Joint Board Basch [?] Seaton [?] Leather [?] Lucas [?] Premir [?] Petitions Ogid [?] and Hardt [?] [Total negs: 45], Jan 15, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11755)
    - Jt. Bd. Hudson Bay 150 Meeting Portraits [Total negs: 65], Jan 19, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11756)
    - Jt. Bd. Gavel Photos [Total negs: 34], Jan 26, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11757)
    - Jt. Bd. For AMWD4 Abe Film [?] glass Meeting at Amenimic [?] Hotel [Total negs: 16], Feb 26, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11758)
    - Freedom Festival Fort Orange, N. J. [Total negs: 53], Mar 14, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11759)
    - Misc. Photos [Total negs: 23], Mar 26, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11760)
    - Jt. Bd. Grove Press Bleeker & Mercer Sts. [Total negs: 49], Apr 13, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11761)
    - Jt. Bd. William [?] Moore Photos & Poems [Total negs: 52], Apr 27, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11762)
    - 2 New Shops Bob Gibson New Jersey [Total negs: 57], May 22, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11763)
    - pensioners Check Presentation [Total negs: 12], Jun 4, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11764)
    - Goldsmith -- Radel. [?] Newark, N. J., Jun 19, 1970 (Box 12, Item 11765)